Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, pre-1991; Series 1
  - Achor, Susan, Dextran-Charcoal Assay for Colchicine Binding Protein., 1973? (Box 13)
  - Ackerman, Stuart E., Radiation Injury of the Lung as Observed by Scanning Electron Microscopy., 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Agosti, Jan M., Induction of Transient Glucose Intolerance with Bovine Growth Hormone C3H and ob/ob Mice., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Al-Sadir, Sadick Jafar, The Influence of Anxiogenic and Anxiolytic Drugs on the Behavior and Physilogy of Socially Housed and Isolated Squirrel Monkeys., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Aladjem, Eva, The Physiology of a Novel Type of Fast Muscle Controlling the Fins of the Pacific San Dan, Citharichthys sordidus., June, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Albin, Penny, A Study of the Effects of Calcium Deficiency on Serum Lipids in Rats., April, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Alder, Janet, S100 Protein and mRNA in Rat Astrocyte Culture: In Situ Hybridization with Coding and Noncoding Regions., June, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Anderson, Wendie T, Distinct Epitopes on I-A and I-E Gene Products Identifies by Monoclonal Antibodies., 1981 (Box 1)
  - Andrewa, David W., The Isolation of Dopaminergic Vesicles from Rat Straitum., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Appleman, J. Alex, Development of a Novel Prometer Probe Vector for Analysis of Rhizobium Promoters., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Arnsdorf, Bobby, Purification of the Intermediate Filament Subunit Protein Vimentin., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Ashcraft, Michael W., Some Thoughts on How to Bring the Idea of Environmental Responsibility to Reality., Spring, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Atha, Kerry Marie, The Behavioral and Physiological Responses of Male Squirrel Monkeys to the Presence of a Live Snake: The Role of Early Experience., June, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Atilano, Lorraine Christine, The Effects of Malnutrition and Exogenous Growth Hormone on Insulin-like Growth Factors and IGF Binding Proteins in the Neonatal Rat., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Augustyn, Damien, The Effects of Transfer RNA on Ovalbumin Synthesis in Estrogen Stimulated Chicks., April, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Babcock, Debra A and Narver, Ellen L., The Effects of Imipramine, Chlorimipramine and Fluoxetine on Canine Cataplexy., June 1976 (Box 1)
  - Bach, Bruce Allen, Investigations Concerning the Isolation and Characterization of the Products of Cycloheximide-Resistant Protein Synthesis in the Mitochondria of Neurospora crassa., September, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Bachelor, Eric Paul, An electrophoretic Study of Taricha Hemoglobin., Spring, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Bagdadi, Daniel, Intracranial Administration of 8-OH-DPAT and Propranolol: Effects on Sexual Behavior in Male Rats., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Baisch, Eugene M., Comparative Effects of Five Calcium Antagonists on Isolated Rabbit Heart and Thoratic Aorta., May 1982 (Box 1)
  - Baldo, Angela M., Population Genetics of the "Alba" Polymorphism on Colias., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Baron, Rebecca M., Removal of Mitomycin C Interstrand Cross-links from the Human C-FMS and C-FOS Oncoenes., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Bartell, Thad Edward, Sex Differences and Laterality Effects in Perception of Alphabetical and Three-Dimensional Stimuli., April 1979 (Box 1)
  - Bassett, James B., Jr., and Fisher, George A., Jr., Aspects of Osmoregulation in Tigriophus Californicus., March 1976 (Box 1)
  - Bauer, Eugene A., See Suen, Patrick W.. (Box 1)
  - Baum, Linda Gwen, Preliminary Investigations of Replication of Double Minute Chromosomes and an Amplified Gene Sequence., June 1979 (Box 1)
  - Bauman, Jeffrey S., The General Ecology of the Palo Alto Baylands with Respect to Man's Influences on the Area., Spring 1970 (Box 1)
  - Beard, Virginia Lee, The Effect of the Lateral Lie on the Spacin of Fish in Schools., June 1979 (Box 1)
  - Beaufait, David W., Some Aspects of Esterase in Two species of Colias Butterflies., 1975? (Box 1)
  - Begley, Diana Lynn, Immunohistochemical Characterization of Primary Cultures of Fetal Mouse Spinal Cord., 1981 (Box 1)
  - Beighle, Chryl Lynn, High Resolution Human Chromosome Banding Studies., February, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Beller, Richard A., Studies in Viability of a Temperature Sensitive Mutant Defective in DNA Replication., 1972 (Box 1)
  - Benson, Mark R., Mechanisms of Reorganization and Lysis in Collagen-Overlaid Human Endothelial Cells., June 1982 (Box 1)
  - Berlot, John, Guidance of Neuronal Growth Cones in the Antennae of the Grasshopper Embryo., 1983 (Box 1)
  - Bertelsen, Carl Andrew, A Single Cell Assay for Nerve Growth Factor and the Seach for NGF Receptor Site., March 21, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Biggins, Susan, The Relationship Between Rate of LDL Oxidation and LDL Subclass Pattern., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Billigmeier, Steve L., Analysis of Vitamin D Receptors in Mouse and Rat Muscle Cells., June 13, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Billinglsey, Kevin G., Thermal Characteristics of Midbrain Raphe Neurons in the Unanesthetized Rat., June 1985 (Box 1)
  - Birch, Barry D., L-Phenylisopropyladenosine (L-PIA) Diminishes Halothane Anesthetic Requirements and Decreases Noradrenergic Neurotransmission in Rats., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Bird, Jeffrey W., Variable Transcription Termination and Posttranscriptional Oligoadenylation of the Large and Small Ribosomal RNAS in Mouse Mitochondria., June 1982 (Box 1)
  - Bobson, Craig M., Techniques for Culturating Sevaceous Gland Cells in Vitro: The Effects of Tetracycline on Cell Outgrowth and a Comparision of Normal and Acne Serum on Lipid Synthsis., 1978 (Box 1)
  - Bock, Clay and J. Paul Elliot, Effects of Pulsing Electromagnetic Fields on Chondrocytes and Vascular Endothelial Cells in Vitro., 1984 (Box 1)
  - Boseker, Andrea Lynn, Neurological and Histopathological Effects of Hyperbaric Oxygen on Cerebral Injury in Gerbils and Spinal Cord Injury in Rats., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Boysen, Eric Cornwell, Spatial Patterning in Captive Chimpanzees., 1978 (Box 1)
  - Brain, Robert Donald, Characterization of Blue Light-Induced Cytochrome Reduction in Neurospora Crassa., March 1977 (Box 1)
  - Brainerd, Margaret Ann, Distribution of two Predatory Gastropods., June 1977 (Box 1)
  - Brand, Frederick Warde, III, The Classification of Visual Cortex Cells of the Cat., May 1977 (Box 1)
  - Braun, David, The Isolation and Partial Characterization of Turbulin from Neurosia Crassa., 1975? (Box 1)
  - Braun, Jonathan, Bleomycin and 43 degree hyperthermia: Increased Cell Killing and the Inhibition of Recovery from Potentially Lethal Dosage., 1975? (Box 1)
  - Brett, Peter B, An Investigation of the role of lysosomes in freeze-thaw damage to cells., 1981 (Box 1)
  - Brokschmidt, Carol Lynn, Long term effects of N-Phosphonacetyl-L-Aspartate on growth rate and aspartate trans-cardamylase level of baby hamster kidney cells., 1981 (Box 1)
  - Bromley, Bryann, Chronic epileptiform activity in rabbit hippocampus induced by alumina cream., June 1978 (Box 1)
  - Bronec, Peter Robert, Preliminary studies of neurotransmitters and neurosecretion in the buccal ganglion of the marine nudibranch tritonia diomedia., May 1977 (Box 1)
  - Brooks, Lisa Delevan, A two locus model with phenotypic transmission., 1978 (Box 1)
  - Broughton, Patricia S., Lake Lagunita crustacea: emergence from dry lakebed soil and succession. Winter 1974-75, Winter 1975-76., 1976 (Box 1)
  - Brower, Danny L., Microtubule control of xylem secondary wall desposition in the root of Allium cepa., March 1973 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Brian Michael, An electrophysiologic, physiologic and ecologic assessment of shallow, daily torpor in citellus tereticaudus., 1979 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Christine Margaret, The effect of R factor, R1, on special antibiotic resistances of Salmonella ttphimurium rough core mutants., 1981 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Edward David, Nocturnal sleep variables and daytime sleepiness of normal elderly humans., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Eugene Weldon, Cloning of satellite and adjacent sequences from Drosophila heterochromatin., 1979 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Howard Richard, Adriamycin toxicity in cultured embryonic chick heart cells., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Randy A., An attempt to isolate a product of mitochondrial protein synthesis from neurospora crassa., 1975 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Sherri, The isolation and partial characterization of cytoplasmic mutants of neurospora crassa., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Stephen Kenneth, Vascularization of the abdominal nerve cord of Procambarus Clarkii: anatomical and physiological findings., June 1979 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Vance Meredith, DNA maturation in the cryptic bacteriophage PBSX., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Brundage, Suzy Ingrid, The sequence of a cDNA clone coding for a novel kallikrein from mouse submaxillary gland., April 1986 (Box 2)
  - Bui, Kim L., Recombinant-viral assay for the discrimination of HTLV-1 and HTLV-II., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Burchard, Julia, Localization of the epitope of a monoclonal antibody which inhibits filament formation in Dictyostelium Myosin., 1986 (Box 2)
  - Burchell, Rebecca Bea, Ecological basis of the association between aesculus californica and anthriscus scandicina., May 1977 (Box 2)
  - Bursten, Stuart L., Membrane and bilayer studies utilizing parinaric acid (9, 11, 13, 15-all trans-octadecatetraene) as a flourescent probe., March 1975 (Box 2)
  - Butler, Constance w., Humoral and cell mediated immune responses of squirrel and rhesus monkeys., March 1976 (Box 2)
  - Butler, Lindsay, Transient inhibition of HLA class I gene expession via "antisense" DNA oligomers., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Callaway, Edward Mathey, The effects of reinnervation on the junctional accumulation of fibroblast-like cells in denervated muscle., 1984 (Box 2)
  - Calvo, Ahmed Venancio, Hypothalamic thermosensitivity of three chipmunk species (eutamias speciosus, e. amoenus, and e. minimus)., March 1977 (Box 2)
  - Camarata, Paul J., Normothermic perfusion of the unicalyceal and multicalyceal kidney: an ex vivo study of the contractility of the renal pelvis., May 1982 (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Bruce Gregory, Electroencephalic characterization of penicillin-and bicuculline-induced epileptiform discharges in rabbit striate cortex., 1983 (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Joseph, Genetic analysis of the spore killer region of neurospora crassa., 1984 (Box 2)
  - Carter, Patrick A., Evolutionary genetics of phosphoglucose mutase., 1984 (Box 2)
  - Cartwright, Kimberly D., Studies on cell-substratum on a clonal cell line of rat pheochromocytoma (PC12)., May 1982 (Box 2)
  - Castillo, Diane, Patterns of alpha serum preteins in mutant mice.., 1975 (Box 2)
  - Cendejas, Fernando, Altered Transport as a Mechanism for Methotrexate Resistance in Cultured Xeroderma Pigmentosum.., June, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Chadwick, Nancy, Pl Cotransduction Used to Map Coupling Factor Mutation in Eschericha Coli Genome., 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Chai, Jonathan T., Development of a New Model for Retinal Adhesion.., June, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Chan, Edward, A Structural Homolog og Murine Q10 in Man.., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Chang, Arleen An-Ling, "The Role of Interleukin-6 (IL-6) in Tumor Necrosis Factor (TNF) and Interleukin-1 (IL-1)-Induced Anorexia: Implications on Cancer Cachexia."., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Chang, Carolyn, Transient Expression of UV Irradiated Shuttle Vectors in Cultured Human Cells.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Chang, Cherylee, Autoradiographic Study Using 3H GABA on the Effects of Phenobarbital on GABA Receptors in Mouse Spinal Cord Cell Structure.. (Box 2)
  - Chang, Jacqueline Anne, Membrane Topology of the a Subunit from E. Coli ATP Synthase.., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Chang, James, The Genomic Cloning of Rat Ornithine Decarboxylase Genes.., 1987 (Box 2)
  - Chang, Patricia E., "Transgenic Superoxide Dismutase Overexpression Confers Increased Resistance to Hyperoxia in D.melanogaster."., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Chang, Steven D., Behavioral Characterization: Interaction Between Idazoxan, the alpha2-adrenoceptor, and the 5-HT1A Receptor.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Chao, James J., Inmmunoglobulin Gene Rearrangement as an Aid to the Diagnosis of B-Cell Lymphoma.., 1984 (Box 2)
  - Cheatham, Michael Lee, Multi-Modality Evoked Resposes as a Monitor of the Effect of Whole Body Hyperthermia on the Feline Brain.., June 1985 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Benjamin Kuan, "An in vivo Assay for inversion Events Mediated by Herpes Simplex Virus."., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Chen, Dillon C., "Isolation and Partial Characterization of The Human NGF Promoter."., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Chen, Herbert, The Effect of Anit-Virla (AIDS) Drugs on DNA Polymerases Alpha and Beta From Human Cells.., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Katherine Tsia-Huey, "Effects of hte Cytokines, Tumor Necrosis Factor, IFN-Alpha, and IFN-Gamma, on Carcinoma of the Lung (A549) and Rental Carcinoma (CRL 1611): Possible Relationship of Induced Proteins to Antiproliefrative and Antiviral Effects."., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Chen, Peter Peinshan, A study of electrophoretic variation in the dwarf perch MICROMETRUS MINIMUS.., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Philip Peihai, Polymorphism of la Antigens in a Wild Mouse Population., June 1986 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Richard, Characterization and Preliminary Mapping of Circadian Clock Mutants of Neurospora crassa.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Cheng, Hugo Quinny, The Role of Phispholipase Activation in the Mechanism of Action of Tumor Necrosis Factor.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Chin, H.Paul, "Suppression of Autoimmune Disease in Nonobese Diabetic Mice by in vivo Cytokine Treatment."., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Choi, John, "Effects of Insulin-like Growth Factor-1 in the Cancer Cachexia Model"., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Cholon, Annette C., The Initiation and Spread of Activation of the Iridophore Cells of the Squid, Loligo Opalescens.., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Chueh, Jane Tsung, Stress: development of the hormonal response.., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Claman, David, Comparing Promoter Efficiency During Acute DNA Infections., May 1982 (Box 2)
  - Clark, Kathryn J., The partial mammectomy as an alternative method for producing postnatal malnutrition in the infant rat., June 1976 (Box 2)
  - Clark, Sharon Ann, Experiments studying the possible attachment of a carbohydrate group to the nascent chains of rat liver albumin.., 1975 (Box 2)
  - Cogan, Martin, Lung Ribosomal Alterations Floowing Oxygen Exposure., Spring 1970 (Box 2)
  - Cohan, Frederick M., A computer simulation of hybridization in nature.., 1975 (Box 2)
  - Cohen, Mark S., The Influence of Heat on the INtracellular Uptake of 2-Nitroimidazole Hypoxic Cell Radiosensitizers In Vitro.., May 1982 (Box 2)
  - Colamarino, Sophia A., The Role of Glycine in N-methyl-D-asparate (NMDA) Receptor-mediated Neuro-toxicity.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Collins, Cynthia, Correlation of a Gas Chromatographic Method of Determining Blood Carboxyhemoglobin Levels with a Multicomponent Spectrophorometric Method.., June 9, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Cooke, William J., Dominance hierarchies in captive sea-lions.., Spring 1971 (Box 2)
  - Corbo, Joseph C., The Cloning and Sequencing of a Homologue of the E. Coli cell division gene, ftsZ, in Rhizobium meliloti.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Cordero, Eric Alejandro Sweet, Studies in the Cell Biology and Physiological Action of Neuropeptides in Aplysia Californica.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Corley, David Dickson, Metabolic Studies of Chick Embryo Heart Cells Exposed to Dororubicin.., 1983 (Box 2)
  - Cornell, Robert A., Description and Cloning of an Antigen with a Differential Expression in Dveleoping Drosophila., 1987 (Box 2)
  - Cornett, Carolyn, Study of the Thermosensitivity of Preoptic Neurons in Euthermic Hibernators., 1987 (Box 2)
  - Cotsirilos, Patricia, Interaction of the late acting complement proteins (C5-C9) with nucleated cell surfaces.. (Box 2)
  - Coufal, Frank Jeffrey, A Consideration of the Overexpression/Modification Duality in Oncogenic Deregulation: Expression of c-myc Homologues in Rearranged and Non-rearranged c-myc Loci of American Burkitt's Lymphoma. (Box 3)
  - Covington, Chris, An immunological study of S-100 protein., October 1975 (Box 3)
  - Cowan, Barrett Edward, The Effect of Tin Protoporphyrin on the Bilirubin Production Rate in Newborn Rats.., 1983 (Box 3)
  - Crawford, Jacqueline Sue, Genetic Engineering of a Soluble Hybrid Human/Mouse Class I Antigen.., 1988 (Box 3)
  - Critchlow, Jonathan, The Effects of Int Constitutive Mutations on the Formation of Double Lysogens of Phage Lambo in E. Coli K12.., 1974 (Box 3)
  - Crowley, Jeffrey James, aspects of DNA Replication in Drosophila Embryos., June 2, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Cummings, R. Ray, Changes in cellular migration and intestinal disaccharidases in suckling rats under normal developmental conditions and after hydrocortisone injection.., March 1979 (Box 3)
  - Daggett, Ann S., The Effect of Heat Shock on resisitance to Methotrexate in Chinese Hamster Ovary Cells.., June 1985 (Box 3)
  - Damassa, David A., Effect of Castration on somatic and behavioral sensitivity in female rats.., March 17, 1972 (Box 3)
  - DasGupta, Hinolda, Elucidation of the Relationship Netween Two Myogenic Regulators Using Mutant Myoblast Lines.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Date, Elaine Satomi, The role of Sterols in the mechanism of Circadian rhythms in Neurospora Crassa.., 1979 (Box 3)
  - Davis, Jeffrey D., DDE and PCB in Eggs of the Brown Pelican (Pelecamus occidentalis) and in Human Milk.., Spring 1970 (Box 3)
  - Dea, Stanley Kwan, Detection and Quantification of 3-Meth-oxytyramine in Ion-pair Extracted Brain Samples Using High Pressure Liquid Chromatography with Electrochemical Detection.., 1984 (Box 3)
  - Debs, Anthony D., Method for Epitope Analysis of Polyclonal and Monoclonal Antibodies to the Glial Fibrillary Acid Protein.., June 1985 (Box 3)
  - Del Beccaro, Mark Andrew, Behavioral analysis of the escape swimming response in the marine mollusk Tritonia Diomedea.., March 1979 (Box 3)
  - Delashaw, Johnny Bill, Jr., Cholinergic mechanismx and cataplexy in dogs.., March 1979 (Box 3)
  - Deliganis, Anastasia V., Differential Interactions of Dimethyltryptamine (DMT) with 5-HT1A and 5-HT2 Receptors.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Dell'Oca, Rosa L., Optimization of T Cell Cloning and Preliminary Observations of CSF T Cells from Patients with Coccidioidomeningitis.., 1987 (Box 3)
  - Demopulos, Christina M., Molecular Genetics of Human serum Albumin: Resttriction Enzyme Fragment Length Polymorphisms and Analbuminemia.., 1984 (Box 3)
  - Desmond, Laura J., Canine Hip Dysplasia.., Spring 1970 (Box 3)
  - Devaleria, Patrick A., Heterotopic Heart-Lung Transplantation in Rats.., June 1982 (Box 3)
  - Dierssen, Heidi, Comparison of Male and Female Function in Baccharis pilularis.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - DiRaimondo, Charles V., The Utilization of Glycerol by Anthopleura xanthogrammica.., March 1976 (Box 3)
  - Donnelly, Janice Ann, Cytogenetic analysis of a human-mouse hybrid clone carrying a balanced translocation between chromosomes 5 and 6.., 1978 (Box 3)
  - Donohue, Kathleen, The Adaptive Significance of Heat Stability of Colias Phosphoglucose Isomerase.., June 1985 (Box 3)
  - Durham, William H., The health effects of air pollution.., May 24, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Dveirin, Keith Robert, Purification of an Endogenous Digitalis-Like Substance from Bovine Plasma.., June 1985 (Box 3)
  - Edel, Kent M., Abstract of work completed. [abstract only]., March 1976 (Box 3)
  - Edel, Kentworth M., Binding of alpha-bungarotoxin in extracts of rat urinary bladder.., June 1976 (Box 3)
  - Effron, Marc Kersten, Localization of DNA Polymerase III Holoenzyme in a Replicating Complex of Bacillus Subtilis Phage SPP1.., June 1974 (Box 3)
  - Eisner, David Barth, Obese versus normal: differences in motivation for food versus non-food incentives.., Spring 1977 (Box 3)
  - Elliott, J. Paul and Clay A. Block, Effects of Pulsing Electromagnetic Fields on Chondrocytes and Vascular Endothelial Cells in Vitro.., 1984 (Box 3)
  - Ellison, David H. and Ruth Whitham, The Effects of Thalamic Intralaminar Lesions in the Cat on the Eye movements of REM Sleep.., Spring 1974 (Box 3)
  - Eng, Soo Jean, The Neurogenesis of the Cat's Lateral Geniculate Nucleus.., 1984 (Box 3)
  - Evans, Bruce, The role of animal effects in the inhibition zone phenomenon.., Spring 1971 (Box 3)
  - Everson, Martha H., The Buffering Capacities of Thiobacillus acidophilus and Escherichia coli.., May 1982 (Box 3)
  - Fan, Chien-Min, Brain Access Model., 1984 (Box 3)
  - Fang, Meika, A small animal angiographic model to study topographical atherosclerotic change in vivo.., March 1978 (Box 3)
  - Fareed, Marcee, Respiration and Photosythesis in Ramalina Reticulata.., Spring 1970 (Box 3)
  - Feng, John J., Resumption of Intestinal Maturation Upon Reintroduction of Intraluminal Nutrients: Functional and Biochemical Correlations.., 1998 (Box 3)
  - Fischer, Steven Richard, Corticosteroid Inhibitors increase Hepatic Amino Acid Uptake in the Rat.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Fisher, George A., Jr., and James B. Bassett, Jr., Aspects of osmoregulation in tigriopus californicus.., March 1976 (Box 3)
  - Flexner, Charles W., Resource utilization and the role of oak tannins in the behavioral ecology of the acorn woodpecker, melanerpes formicivorous.., April 1978 (Box 3)
  - Frank, Bill, Feedback Inhibition of Insulin Secretion Using Double Chamber Perifusion.., 1983 (Box 3)
  - Frelinger, John, The effect of D(-) and L(+) chloramphhenicol on the circadian rhythm of neurospora.., 1975 (Box 3)
  - French, Loretta J., The population biology and ecology of the two grasshopper species Trimerotropis suffusa and Circottetix rabula.., April 1974 (Box 3)
  - Friedman, Sonia, The Role of Auction Potential Activity in Neuronal Cell Death During Deveopment.., 1988 (Box 3)
  - Gale, Arnold D., Family planning as an approach to population control.., Spring 1971 (Box 3)
  - Gale, Scott, Purification of Vimentin From Sheep Scitic Nerve.., June 1985 (Box 3)
  - Gall, Lawrence F., A numerical and taxonomic study of the North American members of the butterfly genus Colias (Lepidoptera: Pieridae).., 1978 (Box 3)
  - Gallegos, Maria, The Morphological and Chemical Variations of Leucosolenia eleanor in the Monterey Bay.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Gawande, Atul, Photophobia in Retinitis Pigmentosa and other studies of the retina and of laser-tissue interaction.., 1987 (Box 3)
  - George, Charles P., An autoradiographic Comparison of Neural Metabolism During Induced Hypothermia and Hibernation.., May 1982 (Box 4)
  - George, Michael Joseph, Changes in Regional Brain Metabolism with Development.., 1984 (Box 4)
  - Gerardo, Charles, Orthotopic and Heterotopic Xenotransplantation of Human Pancreatic Cancer in Severe Combined Immunodeficient (SCID) Mice.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Gibson, Richard F., A preliminary investigation of the effects of alfalfa solubles and commerically prepared fibers in purified diets for young guinea piga.., March 1976 (Box 4)
  - Glaser, Francis Edward, Jr., Characteristics of a Photosynthate Translocating Factor that Acts on Symbitic Chloroplasts in Elysia hedgepethi.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Glasson, Julie R., The Effects of Fish Oil on the Rat Heterotopic Cardia Allograft.., 1988 (Box 4)
  - Glick, Andrew Jeffrey, Socioeconomic factors and childhood diarrhea in Panama.., 1980 (Box 4)
  - Goldman, Jonathan H., Isolation and Characterization of Suppressors of a Missense Mutation in Silent Information Repressor Gene 4 in Saccharomyces Cerevisiae.., May 1982 (Box 4)
  - Goldminz, David, Influence of cell dissociation and culture of chick embryo ventricle on intropic responses to calcium and lanthanum.., December 1977 (Box 4)
  - Goldstein, Dov, The Role of Protein Synthesis in the Inhibition of Macrophage Degradation of Acetyl-Low Density Lipoprotein by Interferon Gamma.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Goldstein, Lynn, EcoRI Endonuclease Cleavage Map of Bacteriophage P4 DNA.., December 1974 (Box 4)
  - Gomez, Richard L., An association between two west coast polyplacophorans (Chitons), Nuttallina californica and Cyanoplax dentiens.., 1975 [?] (Box 4)
  - Gontero, Elizabeth K., Predation on Colias butterflies.., 1981 (Box 4)